It's that time of year again.
Where are more people to their local beaches
to try to feed this heat?
It's a sight to see.
The shore is so fast with umbrellas,
you can hardly see the sand.
We're live at the Yulegahapa beach
where it looks like a...
A swimsuit?
Huh? You okay?
What's wrong?
Hobotone, there you are!
I've been looking for you everywhere.
So?
So, what game should we play today?
None.
We could hit the pool and shout Marco Polo.
No.
How cute!
She's totally rejecting me!
What about you?
Did you bring your swimsuit?
I did.
Stupid Yozara told me to, just in case.
We're here.
You're so hilarious.
Huh.
A horse?
I never would have guessed I'd encounter the demon Astaroth in a place like this.
Wait, I thought the evil gate was destroyed during the last war between God and the devil.
Stop it. You're creeping me out.
Yozara?
That's Yozara?
Indeed.
What are you doing dressed up like that, you weirdo?
It's creepy.
Don't. Stay back.
Get away from me, freak. You're gross.
Ah! Damn it! What was that for?
Someone want to tell me what's going on?
Today is swimsuit day.
It is?
Yeah, the plan was to wear swimsuits all day at the club.
Why would we do that?
Because it would be a shame not to wear my swimsuit after all the money I spent.
This is all your fault. You just had to go home.
The pool was too crowded. It was impossible to have any fun.
You could barely get in, much less find a place to sit.
Are you serious?
Uh, yeah, I am.
Ugh.
So what's going on?
Like, why in the hell are you wearing that horse mask?
Not to mention the full-bodied zebra swimsuit.
It's embarrassing to show your skin in front of a bunch of strangers.
And like you said, the pool is packed.
With this outfit, my flesh isn't exposed and no one can see my face.
So I can keep my dignity.
If you went to the pool wearing that ridiculous thing, everyone would hate you.
They can hate me all they want.
There's no rule that says I can't wear a horse mask.
Yeah, maybe not, but I'm pretty sure there's a rule against freak shows.
Then they wouldn't let you in either.
You take that back!
When you walk into a swimming pool, everyone immediately starts crawling.
Hey, Kodaka.
Uh.
Rika's wearing a swimsuit under her coat.
Want to take a look?
Uh, not really.
Rika thinks you'll like it a whole lot.
You're such an idiot!
It's called the Emperor's New Swimsuit.
That's no suit.
That's going nude.
Why don't you sneak a peek then?
Knock it off, all right?
Rika's just pulling your chain.
Come on.
Tell Rika how she looks.
You look pretty normal.
What?
Normal?
It might seem that way on the outside, but this suit's special.
Once it gets in hot water, it's completely see-through.
Rika will take him to a private secluded hot spring.
He'll think Rika's wearing a regular swimsuit,
but before his very eyes, she'll emerge from the hot water totally naked.
Kodaka will lose control and give in to his carnal desires rising up from deep within.
Not gonna happen.
I wouldn't go to a hot spring with you, not if my life depended on it.
Why not?
Hey!
Big bro, it's you!
Oh!
Ah!
Ow.
Oh!
The monster!
There's a monster in here!
No, it's okay.
She's just-
Guess what, little girl?
I'm gonna eat you.
Oh, please don't do that!
I'm raw!
I don't taste good raw!
Don't worry, I'll throw you on the grill first.
No, I still won't taste good!
Not even then!
Plus, all I've been eating are vegetables!
Good, because I'm a vegetarian.
Oh, no!
If I would have known this was gonna happen,
I never would have stopped eating steak.
I would have given myself a nice, fat, fluffy-
She doesn't eat steak?
Weird.
Recently, Maria changed her diet.
She decided she was really into normal eating.
Coo-coo-coo!
Do it, horse devil!
Take that girl out!
Start at the head and munch your way down
to the toes of that snobby agent of God!
Okay, this is just getting ridiculous.
Ah!
I see!
You're a friend of the bloodsucker, aren't you?
You and that stupid moronic poophead of a vampire
can both rot in hell!
Coo-coo-coo!
It's time for you to die!
I like my little girl's medium rares
who have to write those on a grill at supper's time!
You look so good!
Okay, Yozora, I think she's had enough.
Oh, all right.
Oh, no!
It turned into Yozora!
Be gone now, you devil!
The mask has secret dark powers.
If you put it on,
the demon Astro takes over your body and possesses you.
Now the power's taking over my hands.
I can't see anything!
It's bit black in here!
Coo-coo-coo!
I got some bad news for you, church lady.
The power of darkness has now fully invaded your mind.
But I don't want to be a horse monster forever!
Help me!
Coo-coo-coo!
If you really want help,
then swear you'll never go near my brother again.
Never!
I love big brother!
Don't you dare say you love him, you stupid head!
It's off!
You just broke the curse!
That's what you get, turd!
Why, you...
You...
You what?
Ho bag!
Yozora, I've got an idea.
Since you don't want your swimsuit to go to waste,
how about we go to the beach?
But that place is packed to the brim with people.
We could always go to my family's private beach instead.
Wait, private beach?
Yeah, we've got a place right by the water.
It figures, rich girl.
Well, to be completely honest,
I've only been there one time,
back when I was a little kid.
Besides, it's so far away,
you have to plan to stay overnight.
Hold on!
Does that mean we'd be able to go out there
and hold a training camp sometime over the summer?
Oh, yeah.
I guess we could.
Actually, that sounds really fun.
Like an overnight club field trip.
Plus, this could be a perfect experience
to prepare all of us
for what life will be like
when we become happy people.
Sounds good.
I'll ask my daddy then.
So, it's okay to set it up?
Does anyone have any plans they know about?
I'm guessing we're free.
I mean, let's face it,
it's not like we have any friends.
Way to bring the whole room down.
But wait!
I don't know what a training camp is!
Huh.
We will need an advisor.
Good point.
Huh?
Hey.
Uh, hello?
Hi there.
This is Senna Kajiwazaki.
Is Kodaka available?
Relax, Senna.
Don't you know this is my cell phone number?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Right, I knew that.
So, what's going on?
Uh, are you free today by any chance?
Kobito, too.
Yeah, just have to drop by the club after lunch.
Great!
Then come to my house.
Why?
Do you remember what you said before?
About wanting to pay respects to my father.
Yeah, but this is kinda out of nowhere.
Well, the thing is,
when I asked him about us using the summer house,
I mentioned your name.
And now Daddy says he wants to meet you ASAP.
How come?
I don't know.
Would you mind coming over?
Uh, yeah, I'll be there.
Great, I guess all you'll need are directions then.
Cool.
Let me write them down.
The due date's written down on the card.
He won't be there.
Ugh.
Oh, yeah.
We'll be there.
Oh, wow.
All right, here we go.
Um, hello.
Good day to you both.
Thank you for coming all this way.
I am president of the academy,
but I moonlight his son his dad, too.
Uh, it's very nice to meet you, sir.
My name is Kodaka.
This is my younger sister, Kobito.
Has anyone told you that you look exactly like your father?
This one's lucky enough to have Iri's lovely face.
Please dine with us.
Come.
This way.
Sir, wait.
It's extremely rude to invite someone into your home
without giving them your name first.
Right.
I'm Mr. Kashiwazaki.
That's my name.
But you can call me Heavenstud.
Wait, Heavenstud?
That's really your name?
No, his name's Pegasus.
Pegasus?
How dare you insult me by calling me that!
Sorry.
It's just, people made fun of me a lot in high school.
I'm real sensitive.
No, I understand.
My name's Stella.
I'm the official steward of this house.
Steward?
Please don't stare at me like that, sir.
It makes me uncomfortable.
I fear you might get me pregnant.
Ugh.
Is a steward the same thing as a butler?
At first, I thought Stella was Sina's mother.
Sorry, this is all so new to me.
My wife's currently vacationing around the world.
I gotta say, I'm surprised.
It's not very often you take the time
to greet our guests at the door, Daddy.
That's true.
He's been very anxious about meeting the two of you.
He hasn't stopped talking about it all week.
Hey!
I have not been anxious about anything.
Now bring out the damn food already.
As you wish, sir.
Wow!
Everybody dig in.
Thanks for the food!
Go ahead.
Eat as much as you like.
Don't forget manners, okay?
Thanks for the food.
Oh, yeah.
Um, sir, thank you for helping us get into the academy.
It seems like my dad asked you for a pretty big favor.
That's true.
It was indeed.
Right when the entrance season is over, I hear from him.
That idiot father of yours called me up out of the blue
and all but demanded you better let my son and daughter
in that fancy school of yours.
Well, I'm very sorry about that.
Hmm.
You two aren't exactly the same.
Unlike him, you know what manners are.
That's right.
Here.
It's our way of saying thank you.
Hmm?
Well, what is it?
A world-famous spicy sesame oil.
Next time you cook a meal, add in a little bit of this,
and I promise you won't regret it.
Thank you?
Well, trust me, it can make everything taste better.
It goes good with rice, pasta, really anything.
Even Kobito likes it, and she hates spicy food.
Do you mind if I open one?
Please, go ahead.
That's good.
You're right.
This stuff is awesome.
Glad you like it.
Me too.
I want some.
Well, then your big sister will feed you some more.
Well, maybe you're more like him than I thought.
He was always the master of finding unusual spices for his food.
Thank you.
I guess that's what happens when you move around from town to town your whole life.
He's out traveling right now, as a matter of fact.
After all these years, the man's not changed.
I'm not surprised.
That must have been hard on you kids.
Unbelievable.
Devoting his wasted life to digging up ruins
and then dragging his own kids into it.
The scum.
He's not scum!
I'm sorry.
Sir, I don't think it's fair to call my dad scum.
He's just a hardworking guy.
Oh, you don't have to tell me.
I know.
Stay here?
Tonight?
It's not an imposition at all.
Uh, it's not that.
It's just...
Actually, on weekends, the buses stop at 8.
So it looks like you don't have much choice in the matter.
Huh?
Uh...
If you absolutely have to get home tonight,
I suppose it's possible I could give you a ride.
But honestly, it would be a pain.
Right.
We don't want that, do we?
Come on, just stay over.
But we didn't bring pajamas or anything.
That's no excuse.
You can wear mine.
That's what your old man used to do whenever he spent the night.
And, Kobito, I've got an old pair of PJs that would fit you perfectly.
Um, well, but where will we...
We have a guest room you can sleep in.
I don't know.
Thank you for the kind offer.
Aw, she's cute when she's sleeping, too.
Don't touch her.
You'll wake her up.
My daddy likes you.
I'm surprised that doesn't happen often at all.
It's been a long time since I've seen him in a good mood like this.
I'd hate to see his bad mood.
He really loved you.
Bro, what happened?
Where are we?
You're at my house, silly.
How about you and me take a bath together before bed?
A bath?
But why?
Uh, hey, Kobito, it wouldn't hurt you to skip a night.
Come on, let's get you cleaned up.
Uh, president?
Care for a nightcap?
I appreciate it, sir, but the thing is, I'm a miner.
Relax, will ya?
It's regular grape juice.
Have a drink with me.
I don't know about this.
Mine?
It's the real deal.
Sure you don't want to trade?
No, it's like I said, I'm a miner.
Just kidding.
Back in the day when we were students, your dad and I drank this stuff by the barrel.
That's cool.
I guess I'm standing in for my dad.
Way to take it down, son.
Hey, it's just grape juice, right?
Uh, are you gonna be okay?
Huh?
I'm fine.
Why?
He chugged it down like water.
Back in our student days, your dad and I used to love to drink this.
A lot.
Back in our student days, we used to drink.
It was good.
You all right?
Please, sir.
You've really got to wake up.
Uh, how do you feel?
I wonder if I should let Stella know.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Big bro!
What happened to you?
No, it's not, wait.
Don't run away!
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
What in the world are you doing out here spying on me?
You stupid, perverted, disgusting, molesting, peeping Tom freak boy!
Hey, that's no way to talk to one of your father's guests, is it?
My life is over!
Why'd she go outside?
Beats the heck out of me.
Well, well, well, looks like Kodaka's a pervert.
No way, this isn't what it looks like, I promise!
Don't worry, I know.
Come, let's get you to bed while you still have a chance.
Wait, the president got drunk on wine and fell asleep in there.
Once he's out, there's no way he'll get out of bed till morning,
especially when he's been drinking heavily.
Huh?
I'll put her to bed in the servant's quarters.
She should be just fine there for the rest of the night.
I'm very sorry, but there's no more room.
You and the master of the house are going to have to share a bed tonight.
Um, can I sleep in the servant room?
I sleep naked and don't want to get pregnant.
Fine, then, I'll just go sleep with him.
You and my dad used to drink wine together back in the old days.
Cool.
There's no question.
The president thinks of my dad as being one of the closest friends he's ever had.
That makes sense.
I guess that's why dad felt comfortable leaving me and Kobito behind to go off on his own.
It does make you think.
I wonder if I'll ever make a friend like that someday.
Well, we're off.
Thank you so much for letting us both stay the night.
Of course.
Kobito?
Uh, okay.
Um, thank you.
The food was good.
You're welcome here anytime you like.
Thanks.
That's very kind.
Next time, how about we take another hot bath together?
No!
Huh?
Kobito!
No!
She's freaked.
What did you do to her?
Don't look at me.
I didn't do a thing.
That aside, Kodika?
Huh?
What's up?
Uh, well, I...
I wanted to talk to you about what happened last night.
Huh?
What do you mean?
It's all a blur.
Your dad made me chug wine with him after dinner.
I can't remember a single thing that happened.
Did I do something?
Uh, well, no.
Nothing at all!
Hey, Kobito!
Wait for me!
Hmph.
Sometimes it's best to say you don't remember, even if it's a lie.
Oh, Kodika?
Yeah.
Hey!
Let go of me!
Do this much.
Take care of my daughter.
Huh?
Yes, of course.
Pegasus.
You twerp!
I gotta go.
Thank you so much.
Dumb, dumb, da-dumb, dumb, dumb.
Stella, what are you...
What are you...
Huh?
Jay?
Hey?
All right.
When I woke up in the morning,
an old man's sleeping face was only centimeters away from me.
Hayato.
Oh, no, you say my dad's name in your sleep?
Where did you come from? Why are you in my bed?
What in the name of everything holy is going on here?
I'm Kodaka, Hayato's son, and this is supposed to be my bed.
You're the one who got wasted and...
So you're saying nothing happened.
Sorry, you're not my type.
Next, no one sleeps at camp.
Really, if you're telling me little white lies,
I swear I will never forgive you.
That's actually kind of cute.
Yolanda, baby
I like this anyway.
I see.
When you see me in your Facebook,
I'm still empty.
I'm sorry.